ACTWU's Engineering Department Records 5619/024
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ACTWU's Engineering Department Records
1947-2000
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Engineering Department.
Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Engineering Department.
United Needeltrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE). Engineering Department.
5619/024
10 cubic feet
10 linear feet
Correspondence, reports, publications.
This collection consists of correspondence, reports, newspaper clippings, and files from the Engineering Departments of the Textile Workers' Union of America, Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers' Union, and UNITE.
6766145
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff
Date completed:
July 2010
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, March 2011
Biographical / Historical
The Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, the most significant union representing workers in the men's clothing industry, was founded in New York City in 1914 as a breakaway movement from the United Garment Workers. Radical and immigrant workers in the tailors' and cutters' locals were the core of the seceding group, which advocated industrial unionism and economic strikes in opposition to the UGW's craft organization, which they saw as conservative and timid. Their diverging views had come to the fore during the historic 1910 dispute at the Chicago firm Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. The opposition called the strike against the UGW leadership's advice, and reached a path-breaking agreement with management that established an arbitration system to settle disputes.
Members flocked to the new union. Around 50,000 strong at its founding, by 1920 the ACWA counted about 170,000 members. Initially composed mostly of immigrants of Jewish European descent with Socialist leanings, the ACWA quickly welcomed members of a great number of nationalities and diverse backgrounds. Like in other garment unions, most workers and many members were women, but the leadership was predominantly male, a situation that did not change for many decades. Early on the union adopted a centralized administrative structure combined with industrial unionism, with the joint boards' by-laws having precedence over those of locals.
Espousing a philosophy perhaps brought over by its early immigrant socialist members, the Amalgamated went beyond bread and butter issues and adopted a distinctive form of social unionism that was largely absent in the American labor movement. Starting in the 1920s, it provided educational opportunities and recreational facilities for its members, as well as services such as an insurance plan, banks offering personal loans at low interest rates, low-cost housing cooperatives, medical clinics, and even union-owned restaurants.
Sidney Hillman was the first president of the new union and the most important officer in its history. He applied his experience as bargaining representative in Chicago to the whole industry. Under his leadership the union made significant strides in securing better wages and working conditions for its members, and at the same time it consolidated gains and provided stability to the industry through the widespread adoption of the arbitration system tested at Hart, Schaffner, and Marx. Hillman paid close attention to industry issues, such as production, pricing, and marketing. In order to help management meet the competition of non-union firms, the union conducted studies of efficiency, work methods, and factory costs. Letters to the official publication of the union, Advance, document the controversy that ensued within the union over what was perceived to be collaboration with management.
Hillman also understood the importance of labor's involvement in national affairs and political action. In the 1920s the ACWA sent delegates to the Conference for Progressive Political Action and to the Farmer-labor party conventions. Although many members and officers were Socialists, the union stopped short of officially endorsing the party. Communist attempts at gaining influence within the union were firmly curbed. Hillman's participation in national affairs and politics became prominent during the New Deal, when he became a close advisor to Franklin D. Roosevelt on labor and economic issues. He also served on the board of the National Recovery Administration. Later, during World War II, he helped establish the Labor's Non Partisan League. He was also named associate director of the Office of Production Management, which assisted in mobilizing the nation's resources for the war effort. Hillman's prestige perhaps reflected the healthy condition of his union, which by the end of the conflict was strong and stable.
During the post World War II period the union faced a number of significant challenges. Membership continued to grow (peaking at 395,000 in 1968), but the union's political influence and visibility in national affairs declined. In their never ending pursuit of lower production costs, many firms relocated to the South, forcing the union to engage in large organizing efforts. Simultaneously, signs began to appear of changes that would lead to the almost complete demise of the domestic apparel industry and, ultimately, to the erosion of union membership. Foreign imports of cheap clothing goods steadily grew in the 1950s and 1960s, and mushroomed in the following two decades, plunging employment in the apparel sector into a steady decline. Union efforts to stem the tide included Buy American campaigns and extensive lobbying in Congress, but they were to no avail. In 1976, the ACWA merged with the Textile Workers of America to become the Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Despite successful and much publicized nationwide actions such as the Farah boycott and the J.P. Stevens corporate campaign, the woes threatening the union's existence continued unabated. The fate of the domestic industry was sealed in the late 1970s and the 1980s by the flight of firms chasing tax breaks and cheap labor abroad. By 1995, when ACTWU voted to merge with the International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union, their combined membership was 350,000. The new Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees (UNITE!) seemed poised to infuse new life in a troubled union.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related collections: 5619: Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America And all other 5619 collections.
Textile industry--New York (State)--New York; Textile workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Clothing trade--New York (State)--New York; Clothing workers--Labor unions--New York (State)--New York; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union --Archives.; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Engineering Department--Archives; Brand-Rex Company --Archives; C. H. Masland & Sons --Archives; Devro, Inc. --Archives; Ensign Bickford Company --Archives; International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union --Archives.; Johnson & Johnson --Archives; Microfibres, Inc. --Archives; Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corporation --Archives; Permacel, Inc. --Archives; Phoenix Dye Works --Archives; Superior Trim Company --Archives; Textileather Corporation --Archives; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees --Archives.; UNITE HERE (Organization) --Archives
6766145
- Brand-Rex Co, Willimantic, CT, 1979-1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Ensign Bickford Co., Simsbury, CT, 1978-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Kraft Hat Co., Bronx, NY, 1991-1997 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Superior Trim Co., Findlay, Ohio, 1977-1993 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Liz Claiborne. Secaucus, NJ, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- CH Masland &Sons Carlisle-PA, 1970-1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Maidenform. Jacksonville, FL, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- NCC Industries (Maidenform) Cortland, NY, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Microfibers, INC., -Pawtucket RI, 1983-1994 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Morgan Shirtmakers. Morgantown West Va., 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Charles Navasky Co. Philipsburg, PA, 1990-1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Owens-Corning Fiberglass Corp-Huntingdon, PA, 1955-1991 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Owens-Brockway, Belvidere, NY, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Palm Beach Co.-Erlanger &Newport KY, 1981-1995 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Palm Beach Co.-Knoxville Tennessee, 1971-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Palm Beach Co.- Talladega, AL, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Permacel INC, New Brunswick, NJ, 1975-1995 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Phoenix Dye Works - Cleveland, Ohio, 1977-1997 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Schlegel Inc, -Rochester, NY, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Swift Textiles, Inc-Erwin, NC, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Textileather. Toledeo, OHIO, 1981-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Thomas Bradford. Huntingdon, TN, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Tultex, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Tultex Corporation-South Boston, NC, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Tultex Corporation. Martinsville, VA, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Warnaco Knitwear Division of Puritan Sportswear. Duncansville, PA, 1980-1986 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Johnson & Johnson-General, 1976-1986 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Johnson & Johnson International Shipping Center-New Brunswick, NJ, 1975-1977 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Johnson & Johnson. Ethicon, NJ, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Johnson & Johnson-Baby Products, Shipping, etc.-New Brunswick, NJ, 1976-1980 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Devro, INC. (Johnson & Johnson) - Somerville NJ, 1975-1996 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Johnson & Johnson. Ethicon, NJ, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Johnson & Johnson- Chicago & Park Forest Illinois, 1970-1989 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Johnson & Johnson-Chicago Illinois, 1981 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Johnson & Johnson, Eastern Diaper Place, Skillman, NJ, 1978-1986 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Ethicon, Incorporated-Somerville, NJ [folder 1 of 2], 1986-1985 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Ethicon, Inc.-Somerville, NJ [folder 2 of 2], 1979-1986 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Johnson & Johnson Eastern Surgical Dressing Plant, New Brunswick, NJ, 1976-1978 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Fall River Shirt CO. - Fall River Massachusetts, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- William Brooks Shoe Co. Nelsonville Ohio, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Bristol Lingerie-Bristol, VA, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Cranston Print Works-Webster Division, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Howard Daniels Reports & Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Andrew Wnorowski. Reports & Correspondence, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Ava Pearl-Scheduled Plant Trips, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Howard Daniels-Scheduled Plant Trips, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Andrew Wnorowski- Scheduled Plant Trips, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1996 Plant Trips-Daniels, Pearl, Wnorowski (Box 3, Folder 6)
- H. Daniels-Reports & Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Ava Pearl Plant Visits, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- H. Daniels Reports and Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Johnson & Johnson Jelco Labs. Raritan, NJ (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Johnson & Johnson Ethicon, Chicago, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Justin Clothing, New Bedford Massachusetts (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Johnson & Johnson, New Brunswick, NJ Baby Products, Shipping, etc., 1981-1996 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- A. Wnorowski-Reports & Correspondence July, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  Scope and Contents
  July, 1995.
- A. Wnorowski-Scheduled Plant Trips-July, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  July 1, 1993.
- H. Daniels, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- A. Wnorowski-Plant Visits, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Nicholas Reale. Reports & Correspondence, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Nicholas Reale. Reports & Correspondence, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- A. Wnorowski Reports & Correspondence, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Sterlingwear of Boston, Inc.-East Boston, Massachusetts (Box 4, Folder 2)
- State Coat Front Co.-Boston, Massachusetts (Box 4, Folder 3)
- H. Daniels-Reports & Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- H. Daniels, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence [folder 1 of 2], 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence [folder 2 of 2], 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Ava Pearl Reports & Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- H. Daniels Reports & Correspondence, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- American Cyanamid Company, 1958-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Acme Cotton, Inc., 1978-1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Acme Cotton, Inc., 1981-1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Acme Cotton, Inc., 1979-1980 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- American Cyanamid Company, 1953-1960 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- American National Standards Institution, Inc., 1971-1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Armstrong Cork Company: Arbitration - Job Evaluation, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- TWUA File in Arbitration with Armstrong Cork Company, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Textile Workers Union of America in the Matter of Arbitration with Armstrong Cork Company, 1959 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  December 22, 1959
- Armstrong Cork Company, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Burlington Industries Arbitration Erwin Mills Division, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Burlington Industries; Erwin Mills, 1951 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Burlington Industries; Erwin Mills, 1951-1965 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Burlington Mills, 1980-1986 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Columbus Coated Fabrics Arbitration, 1962 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Brooks Brothers, 1995-1994 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Cambridge Towel Mills, 1977-1984 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Celanese Corporation Celco Plant, 1973-1978 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Celanese Corporation Celco Plant, 1971-1975 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Celanese Corporation, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Celanese Fibers Company, 1973-1977 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Celanese Fibers Company, 1971-1973 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Celanese - 1966 Arbitration, 1966-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Celanese - 1966 Arbitration (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Celanese Canada Limited, 1969-1973 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Celanese Fibers Company, 1958-1974 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Workload Arbitration - 1973; Calvin L. McCoy, Arbitrator; Staple Department, Celanese Fibers Company (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Workload Arbitration - 1973; Calvin L. McCoy, Arbitrator; Staple Department, Celanese Fibers Company, 1970-1973 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Celanese: Grievance and Arbitration Study, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Celanese: Grievance and Arbitration Study, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- De Rossi & Son, Company, 1973-1977 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Celanese Corporation, 1980-1987 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Celanese Safety Conference, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Cranston Print Works, 1970-1979 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Cranston Print Works, 1970-1976 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Cranston Print Works, 1980-1994 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Cranston Print Works, 1986-1988 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Cranston Print Works, 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Cranston Print Works, 1982-1984 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Cranston Print Works, 1987-1997 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Cranston Print Works, 1985-1988 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Cranston Print Works, 1983-1985 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Cranston Print Works, 1980-1982 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Cone Mills, Greensboro, N.C., 1947-2000 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Cone Mills, Greensboro, NC & Salisbury, NC, 1981-1992 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Cone Mills, Greensboro, NC & Salisbury, NC, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Columbian Rope Company, 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Columbian Rope Company, 1966-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Duro Textile Printers, 1989-1995 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Duro Finishing Corp, 1978-1996 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1975-1995 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1977-1987 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  March 9, 1989
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1986-1988 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Eagle Knitting Mills, 1985-1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Haartz-Mason, Inc., 1990 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  April 3, 1990
- Harvey Woods, Ltd., 1980-1982 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Harvey Woods, Ltd., 1971-1982 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Hathaway Shirt, 1993-1994 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Hathaway Shirt Company, 1975-1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Health-Tex Arbitration, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Health-Tex Corporation, 1992-1993 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Health-Tex, 1987-1997 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Health-Tex - Diamond Hill Plant, 1982-1983 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Health-Tex - Maine Portland and Gardiner Plants, 1981-1985 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Health-Tex - Maine Portland and Gardiner Plants, 1979-1980 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Health-Tex - Diamond Hill Plant, 1979-1981 (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Health-Tex, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Health-Tex, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  June 6, 1995
- Huyck Canada Limited, 1979-1984 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Kayser-Roth, Limited, 1980-1984 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  French
- Kayser-Roth, Limited, 1971-1982 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Permacel, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Time Study, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Union, 1965-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Johnson and Johnson, 1963-1998 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Mohawk Carpet, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Ensign-Bickford Industries, Inc., 1987-1998 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Time Study, 1996 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Time to Sew One Shirt, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- American Association of Industrial Management of Connecticut, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Armstrong Cork Company, 1947 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- American Institute of Industrial Engineers, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Health-Tex (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Textile Workers Union of America, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- The Maynard Foundation (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Important Calculations, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Textile Workers Union of America, 1965-1979 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Time Study, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1987-1988 (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Contract Clauses Dealing with Piece Rates, Standards, etc., 1965-1975 (Box 8, Folder 23)
- American Association of Industrial Management, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Cost of Living, 1974-1978 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Fein, Mitchell, 1970-1980 (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Incentive Rate - Contract Clauses (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Post Hearing Brief, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Job Evaluation Class, 1975-1992 (Box 8, Folder 30)
- Leadership Conference, 1977-1980 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Allowances for Sewing Operation (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Xerox Exhibits, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Naumkeag Steal Cotton Company Weavers' Arbitration, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, 1982-1991 (Box 8, Folder 36)
- Oneita Knitting Mills, 1976-1982 (Box 8, Folder 37)
- Stearns & Foster Company: Incentive Rates Arbitration, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 38)
- Stearns & Foster Company: Incentive Rates Arbitration, 1969-1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- N. Sumergrade & Sons, Inc., 1976-1986 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- N. Sumergrade & Sons, Inc., 1967-1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1975-1979 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Fieldcrest, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1984-1998 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1991-1994 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1987-1992 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1983-1985 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1980-1982 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1973-1980 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc., 1972 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1949-1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Fieldcrest Mills; Towel Hemmers, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Fieldcrest Mills; Towel Hemmers, 1975-1977 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc.; Foster Winders, Winding Department, 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Fieldcrest Mills; Arbitration - Wash Cloth, 1966-1977 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Fieldcrest Mills; Arbitration - Wash Cloth, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1974-1977 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc., 1975-1982 (Box 9, Folder 20)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1979-1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc, 1970-1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc., 1966-1981 (Box 9, Folder 23)
- Fieldcrest Mills, Inc., 1971-1980 (Box 9, Folder 24)
- Findlay Industries, 1982-1984 (Box 9, Folder 25)
- Findlay Industries, 1986-1996 (Box 9, Folder 26)
- Findlay Industries, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 27)
- Fingerhut Corporation; Alexandria, MN, 1993-1994 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Flushing Shirt Manufacturing Company; Grantsville, MD, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Flock Industries, Inc.; Phillipsburg, N.J., 1980-1984 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- American Viscose Corporation; Parkersburg, W. Va., 1970 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- FMC Arbitration Decisions, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Franco Manufacturing Company - Monroe Print Plant; Charlotte, NC, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Monroe Prints, Inc.; Monroe, NC, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Garden State Tanning Formerly W.D. Byron; Williamsport, MD, 1986-1994 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Fox Point Sportswear; Merill, Wisconsin, 1989-1995 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Hanes; Galax, VA, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Magee Carpet Company; Bloomsbury, PA, 1980-1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Magee Carpet Company; Bloomsbury, PA, 1978-1981 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Pacific Columbia Mills; Columbia, SC, 1982-1988 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Pacific Columbia Mills; Columbia SC, 1981-1982 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Pacific Columbia Mills; Columbia, SC, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Erwin Mills; Erwin, NC, 1979-1991 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Filters Company; Milbury Massachusetts, 1981-1996 (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Felters Company; Milbury, Massachusetts, 1981-1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Farah, Inc.; El Paso, Texas, 1994-1995 (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Harvey Woods, Ltd.; Woodstock, Ontario, 1976 (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Harvey Woods, Ltd.; Woodstock, Ontario, 1969-1976 (Box 10, Folder 21)
- Kendall Mills; Wallpole, Massachusetts, 1972-1984 (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Kendall Mills; Wallpole, Massachusetts, 1975-1978 (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Munsing - Re-Engineering Program, 1980-1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Munsingwear - Re-Engineering Program, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Opelika Manufacturing Company; Opelika, Alabama, 1970-1981 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Pacific Columbia Mills; Columbia, SC, 1975-1979 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Pacific Columbia Mills; Columbia, SC, 1976-1979 (Box 10, Folder 28)